NES for PSP v0.5
                        REi

■ Outline
NES emulator is running on the PSP.
Are based on the Ver.0.95J of InfoNES.
However, to work the farm as long as the PSP v1.0.
(Not tested in v1.50.)

■ How to use
Appropriately to create a folder / PSP / GAME / Memory Stick,
Please put the EBOOT.PBP enclosed. Then, ROM you want to run
Please copy the folder you want more than one in the image.
Please prepare your own ROM. I tried to correspond to the ZIP file.
The background image on the screen with a menu and put in the same folder as the MENU.BMP.

Default operation:
○: A button
×: B button
△: A button (fire)
□: B button (fire)
L: menu
START: Start button
SELECT: SELECT


■ (rather than the source) and reference
Source Hello World, the PSP!
Source of InfoNES v0.95J
Source of RIN
Source of TMK's creation InfoNES v0.94J for PSP
Source of NesterJ for PSP 1.01
Source of PSP Sound
Ruka's source for unzip
Thanks to everyone who has opened the source to the public.
I was allowed to use the icon's pochi.


■ Revision History
v0.5 (2005/06/28)
Further formatting and source.
-Was to be able to compile as it is the source of the InfoNES.
· Replaced InfoNES095J.
• Change from PS2DEV PSPTOOLCHAIN0625 the environment.
Was changed to Read-Peek from the key input.
Anyway left became even more amusing AUTO frameskip.

v0.4 (2005/06/15)
Further formatting and source
Sound, has changed only with the author? (Only to notice?)
Drawing processing has become a little bit faster.
Mill with a full screen.
Mill to add features wallpaper on the menu.
· I changed it to something pochi create the icon.
• Supports Overclocking
• Supports frame skipping AUTO

v0.3b (2005/05/28)
Formatting and the source a little
-Tried to change the icon.

v0.3a (2005/05/24)
• If you press the left at the FRAMESKIP in the menu when using the non-ROM of SRAM
Can select SAVE SRAM. (Does not display)

v0.3 (2005/05/24)
-I was wrong the date of the update history.
• Supports ZIP file menu or from the filer and RIN112_opt_unzip.
-Tried to in the middle of the display position.

v0.2 (2005/05/21)
Anyway all was well-mapper of InfoNES.
Sound and began to go through copying the Mr. TMK.
Add frame skip.
Simple add fire feature.
-I made this Readme.

v0.1 (2005/05/19)
Anyway, pictures came out.